dubaiforums.com 2013-07-14

# Dubai Forums Privacy Policy

At **DubaiForums.com** , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines what types of personal information is received and collected while you browse our website. 

**DubaiForums.com** uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads on it's pages. These third parties may collect and use information (but not your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to show advertisements about goods and services that are of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, you can visit [Google's Advertising and Privacy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) page.

If you wish to opt out of Advertising companies tracking and tailoring advertisements to your surfing patterns you may do so at [Network Advertising Initiative](http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Google uses the Doubleclick DART cookie to serve ads across it's Adsense network and you can get further information regarding the DART cookie at [Doubleclick](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) as well as opt out options at [Google's Privacy Center](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, **DubaiForums.com** makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**   
On some pages, in the forum and gallery **DubaiForums.com** does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**Links**  
**DubaiForums.com** may contain links to other web sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other web sites. We suggest our users to be aware of this when they leave **DubaiForums.com** and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by our website.
